# Jaqueline P. Romero

Rua Ines Maria Cuoghi, 50 – Urbanova / São José dos Campos – SP - Brazil • Cel: +55 (12) 99245-5111 • E-MAIL jaquelineromero@web.de

#### **Personal Summary**

IT Analyst with a strong technical background who possesses self-discipline and the ability to work with the minimum of supervision. Work experience in multinational companies, supporting international clients. Having exposure to a wide range of technologies and solid experience diagnosing hardware and software problems and to ensure that quality solutions meet business objectives while working along with a strong team spirit.

Education

**Degree in Information Technology** 

FMU - Dez/ 2014

**MBA** in IT management

FMU - Dez/2018

**Competences** 

- SAP Supply Chain Data management and SAP MM and SD modules.
- Winshuttle Data Mass Upload.
- SAP MDG.
- IDOC and issues regarding data synchronization.
- Data management knowledge and ability to work with complex data.
- Knowledge in ITIL foundations V3 and IT best practices.
- Active Directory management.
- ServiceNow, HP Service Center and Magic 2.0
- SQL database consultancy .
- Excellent customer facing, communication and rapport building skills.
- Experience of Lotus Notes, Microsoft OS and SAP user's administration.
- Basic knowledge of SAP functionalities and users administration tools.
- HTML, CSS and Front End development knowledge.
- End user support experience.
- Solid problem solving skills.

.....

#### **Work Experience**

## Johnson & Johnson (2017 – current) SAP Master Data Analyst

- Constantly improving the regional material creation process along with the data leads.
- Knowledge on Supply Chain process and product lifecycle.
- Set-up and maintain SAP functions in relation to optimal product procurement.
- Create new product set-up, extensions and interaction with various departments.
- Maintain and own all SKU set-up product forms utilized within teams.
- Maintain item data and proper settings with respect to all "active" and "de-activated" (discontinued) SKUs.
- Maintain all fields and develop and champion the consistency and accuracy of all data in the system.
- Assist in troubleshooting and solving SAP related problems for any department.
- Communicate updates to stakeholders at multiple levels, including those external to the organization

## Mars Brasil (2016 – 2017) Service Desk Analyst

- Successfully delivered IT services in extremely fast-paced, constantly changing environment. Closed 95% of trouble tickets on the first call without escalation.
- Achieved a user satisfaction rating of 4.8/5.0; consistently logged and monitored ticket status to ensure fast, quality resolution of every issue.
- Responsible for supporting clients through multiple support channels,
- Perform password administration and access support for Active Directory, PeopleSoft and internal/proprietary systems and applications.

#### Danfoss (2013 – 2014)

Service Desk Intern

- Substantially contributed to the technical development and innovation along with the teammates, always focusing on the quality and efficiency.
- Responsible for 1º and 2º line IT global support in English and Portuguese through multiple support channels (Phone, email, IM and IT portal).
- Administering the IT department's policies and procedures.
- Troubleshooting PC's, laptops and mobile devices.
- Working closely with software suppliers to resolve operational issues.
- Training new employees on IT policies and best practices.

# Languages and abroad experience

### **International Experience:**

- 3 months of exchange in Germany for language improvement purposes.
- 18 months in Poland.

## Languages:

- Advanced English
- Intermediate Polish
- Basic German
- Intermediate Spanish

#### **Certification & Extra courses**

- HDI Support Center Analyst International Certification
- SAP MM module training
- SQL Trainning (Code Academy)
- ITIL Foundations Prep.